<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-18T13:06:52+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">BandwagonHOST</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/BandwagonHOST.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BandwagonHOST" /><published>2019-06-02T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-06-02T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/BandwagonHOST</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/BandwagonHOST.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;enterprise-servers&quot;&gt;Enterprise servers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use only top-quality, enterprise grade equipment. This reduces downtime caused by hardware malfunctions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;247-service-monitoring&quot;&gt;24/7 Service monitoring&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our staff monitors all services and network non-stop, acting proactively to prevent hardware or network issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;premium-network&quot;&gt;Premium network&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All plans include 1 Gigabit uplink connection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;we-own-our-equipment&quot;&gt;We own our equipment&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not rely on third-party when it comes to hardware equipment. We also own our IP space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;a href=&quot;https://bandwagonhost.com/aff.php?aff=48130&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/bwg_main_banner.jpg&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;BandwagonHOST&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our service is self-managed; this allows us to keep the price down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All VPS nodes are checked every minute for failures and overload.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We perform weekly security audits on our network. Our website is secured with SSL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-our-self-managed-kvm-vps-hosting&quot;&gt;About our Self-Managed KVM VPS hosting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our VPS service is running on KiwiVM, a secure control panel developed in-house. It allows to perform all basic management tasks: start/stop, OS reload, Emergency console, rDNS (PTR) record management, datacenter migration, snapshots, usage statistics, API etc. Virtualization platform is KVM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following Operating Systems are available for your VPS:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CentOS
Debian&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu
Fedora&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All operating systems come in 32 and 64 bit flavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bandwagonhost.com/aff.php?aff=48130&quot;&gt;GO TO BandwagonHOST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Enterprise servers We use only top-quality, enterprise grade equipment. This reduces downtime caused by hardware malfunctions.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/bwg_main_banner.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/bwg_main_banner.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Apple Music</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/AppleMusic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple Music" /><published>2018-02-18T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2018-02-18T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/AppleMusic</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/AppleMusic.html">&lt;p&gt;Stream anything in the Apple Music collection on all your devices ad-free. Download albums, tracks, and music videos to your personal library and play them offline. Start your free three-month trial and cancel anytime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/apple_music1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;45-million-songs-plus-your-entire-itunes-library&quot;&gt;45 million songs. Plus your entire iTunes library.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Music allows you to stream our catalog of 45 million songs, along with everything in your iTunes library, no matter where it came from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;always-ad-free&quot;&gt;Always ad-free&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether streaming your favorite song, album, mix, playlist, or music video, you’ll never be interrupted by ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;play-every-song&quot;&gt;Play every song.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t want to use your cellular data, you can download anything from Apple Music and listen to it offline. No signal required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/apple_music2.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discover-more-music-more-often&quot;&gt;Discover more music. More often.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Music brings you up-and-coming artists and curated playlists every day. Listen to Beats 1 radio for news and culture updates, and if you have a specific music request, just ask Siri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;music-videos-from-today-and-back-in-the-day&quot;&gt;Music videos from today and back in the day.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Music now has the best music videos from the ’80s, ’90s, ’00s, and today’s top artists, with exclusive playlists — all without ads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;create-a-playlist&quot;&gt;Create a playlist.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be your own DJ by easily making a playlist of your favorite songs or music videos. Or let Apple Music create mixes for you based on the music you like the most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;find-new-songs-with-a-little-help-from-your-friends&quot;&gt;Find new songs with a little help from your friends.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create a profile so that you and your friends can see the songs and music videos you’re each checking out, and share what you’re into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/apple_music3.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;try-it-free&quot;&gt;Try it free&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/deeplink?app=music&amp;amp;p=subscribe&amp;amp;at=1010lsZo&amp;amp;ct=IS_EM6&quot;&gt;TRY IT FREE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Stream anything in the Apple Music collection on all your devices ad-free. Download albums, tracks, and music videos to your personal library and play them offline. Start your free three-month trial and cancel anytime.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/apple_music.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/apple_music.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">iPhone X/Edition</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/iPhone.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="iPhone X/Edition" /><published>2017-09-22T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-09-22T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/iPhone</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/iPhone.html">&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/iphone-8.webp&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, Apple’s planning on introducing three new iPhones. The most significant of these is the completely redesigned iPhone X/Edition, which will become the first Apple handset with an OLED display.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This 5.8-inch smartphone may be priced at $999 for a 64GB model, $1,099 for a 256GB model, and $1,119 for a 512GB model. Available color choices should include black, white, and brush copper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other features should include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Water resistance improved to IP68, or perhaps waterproof
-10-nanometer A11 chip
-Wireless Charging, probably using Qi protocol;
-10W USB-C wall charger
-Iris scanning for authentication; infrared face unlock capability
-New sound when charging
-Vertical camera on the back
-The end of the Home button, replaced by facial recognition or a “function area.” No Touch ID on iPhone 8
-Lots of new native wallpapers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 4.7-inch “iPhone 8” and 5.5-inch “iPhone 8 Plus” are expected to retain the design found on the current iPhone models. Beyond this, little is known about these handsets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/iphone-8.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/iphone-8.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">This is the iPhone X</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/iPhoneX.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This is the iPhone X" /><published>2017-09-12T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-09-12T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/iPhoneX</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/iPhoneX.html">&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/iPhoneX.jpg&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple has just unveiled the iPhone X, iPhone 8, and iPhone 8 Plus at today’s special media event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;iphone-x&quot;&gt;iPhone X&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/iPhoneX1.webp&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple CEO Tim Cook announced “One more thing…” as the iPhone X – called iPhone “Ten.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the top new features of the phone is an edge-to-edge 5.8-inch OLED Super Retina display without a Home button. Instead, you’ll simply swipe up for Home or to go to the multitasking screen. Siri can be activated by pressing the enlarged power button on the right side. It will reportedly have 3 GB of RAM to go along with the new A11 Bionic processor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to unlock, the iPhone X uses Face ID. Instead of your fingerprint, your face is how the handset is unlocked. According to Apple’s Phil Schiller, there’s just a 1 in 1 million chance that someone else could unlock your iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Apple Pay, you will double tap the side button and then look at your phone. Any apps that work with Touch ID will also work with the new technology. Face ID is powered by a True Depth camera that learns your face even if you change looks or wear glasses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The front camera can also be used for the new Animoji feature that will allow your face to create fun animated emojis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/iPhone_emoji.webp&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rear camera has dual 12-megapixel lenses that both offer optical image stabilization and a better quad LED True Tone flash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A special Portrait Lighting feature will help provide different types of lighting types to photos and looks great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the front camera will allow users to take Portrait Mode selfies along with the Portrait Lighting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery can also last more than two hours longer than the iPhone 7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With wireless charging features, users can charge their handset with any Qi-enabled technology or the newly announced AirPower. The Apple designed mat can charge an iPhone, Apple Watch, and AirPods with a special case all at the same time. That will arrive sometime next year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can preorder the handset on October 27 and it will ship starting November 3. It will be available in black or silver. It will start at $999 for a 64GB edition and also be available in a 256GB model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;iphone-8-and-iphone-8-plus&quot;&gt;iPhone 8 and iPhone 8 Plus&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/iPhone8.webp&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple also unveiled the iPhone 8 and iPhone 8 Plus. Both handsets are more of an evolutionary take from the current generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both of those handsets will be available to preorder this Friday, Sept. 15 and hit the market one week later Friday, Sept. 22. Buyers can choose from a silver, space gray, or gold handset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 8 Plus will retail for $799 for the 64GB version and $949 for a 256GB edition. The iPhone 8 will cost $699 for a 64GB version and $849 for the larger version.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/iPhoneX.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/iPhoneX.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Apple Watch Series 3</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/appleWatch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple Watch Series 3" /><published>2017-09-02T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-09-02T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/appleWatch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/appleWatch.html">&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/appleWatch.webp&quot; width=&quot;&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No designs changes are expected on the third-generation Apple Watch. Internal hardware changes could prove significant, however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest hardware change could be the introduction of an LTE model for the first time. Other features could include a micro-LED display, better battery, and improved process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the hardware side, new exercise routines could be in the offering. The wearable device could soon be able to track workouts for basketball, bowling, climbing, cricket, cross-country skiing, curling, dance, equestrian sports, fencing, fishing, golf, gymnastics, jump rope, pilates, skating, surfing, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we’ll probably see a new lineup of Apple Watch bands arrive.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/appleWatch.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/appleWatch.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Canary Mail - Encrypted Email</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/CanaryMail.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Canary Mail - Encrypted Email" /><published>2016-07-29T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2016-07-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/CanaryMail</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/CanaryMail.html">&lt;p&gt;This is what iOS Mail should be. Easy encryption, natural language search, instant read receipts and much more are baked right in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magically clean your invox.&lt;/strong&gt; Canary Mail uses algorithms to determine which of your emails is likely to just be junk. A tap on the magic wand and a scroll through your email is all it takes to find, select, and then delete those unwanted junk emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Filters for what you need.&lt;/strong&gt; Canary Mail has built in filters for your unread, starred, and unanswered email. This makes it easy to focus on what’s important when you’re working through your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it-about&quot;&gt;What is it about?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Canary Mail fully supports OpenPGP email encryption in a gorgeous and full-featured way. You can search several key repositories for your contacts, or import their public keys through iTunes File Sharing. That’s how you get your own public and private keys into Canary Mail, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-wo-love-it&quot;&gt;Why wo love it&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does Canary Mail offers great OpenPGP email encryption, but it’s a pleasure to use. You can choose whether to sign and encrypt your email as you send it, assuming you have the recipient’s public PGP key. The unified inbox is gorgeous, and the filters work to make your email time more efficient and productive. The features I depend upon, like instant read receipts and the ability to snooze an email until later, are baked into the app, too. I’ve yet to find a secure email app as gorgeous and fully-functional as Canary。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-screenshots&quot;&gt;App Screenshots&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/CanaryMail1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/CanaryMail2.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/CanaryMail3.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/CanaryMail4.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-store-description&quot;&gt;App Store Description&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you think you can buy Canary and forget it, forget it. It is so delightful to use and behold, we bet you won’t go back to your boring old email app again. And you shouldn’t – this is 2017, and encrypted email is a necessity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KNOW WHEN YOUR EMAILS ARE READ
When you send an email with Canary, you can choose to be notified instantly when your recipient reads your email. This makes emailing more interactive, and enables effective follow-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FOCUS ON WHAT’S IMPORTANT, CLEAR OUT THE REST
Canary automatically identifies important emails and highlights them in the ‘Focused’ Inbox. You can choose to be notified of important emails only. What’s more, you can automatically clear out less important email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FIND WHAT YOU NEED
Canary’s natural language search enables you to find what you need, in the way you think about it. So you could search for “Emails to Tim”, “Photos from dad”, “Spreadsheets this week”, to get the right email or file at the first shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ENCRYPT YOUR EMAIL
Canary is incredibly secure and offers PGP encryption out of the box. To simplify key management, it lets you search for your contacts on Keybase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-it-in-the-app-store&quot;&gt;Get it in the App Store&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/US/app/id1155470386?mt=8&amp;amp;at=11lGBA&amp;amp;ct=IS_R5&quot;&gt;Canary Mail - Encrypted Email&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">This is what iOS Mail should be. Easy encryption, natural language search, instant read receipts and much more are baked right in.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/CanaryMail.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/CanaryMail.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Make it move: Gif Me! Camera</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/gifme.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make it move: Gif Me! Camera" /><published>2015-11-15T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2015-11-15T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/gifme</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/gifme.html">&lt;p&gt;Create and share animated GIFs with Gif Me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add frame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add stickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set the speed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Write text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it-about&quot;&gt;What is it about?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gif Me! is the best way to create and share short video in animated GIF or MP4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-wo-love-it&quot;&gt;Why wo love it&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like to create and share, Gif Me will help you get it done. It’s absolutely loaded with features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-screenshots&quot;&gt;App Screenshots&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/gifme1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/gifme2.jpg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/gifme3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-store-description&quot;&gt;App Store Description&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gif Me! is the best way to create and share short video in animated GIF or MP4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy: capture a small moment with your built in camera, and share it on social networks. You can apply an image filter too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Features –&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Capture frames with camera&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Import photos from your album&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Import a video file&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Import a live photo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Real time color filters&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add a frame, text on the animation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stop motion or video mode&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Send by email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Share on social networks (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can remove watermark in settings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can create stop motion, time lapse, slideshow or wiggle gifs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You like Gif Me!? Please give us 5 stars! Your feedback is very important to our work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-it-in-the-app-store&quot;&gt;Get it in the App Store&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/US/app/id992836853?mt=8&amp;amp;at=11lGBA&amp;amp;ct=IS_R5&quot;&gt;Gif Me! Camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Create and share animated GIFs with Gif Me.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/gifme.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/gifme.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">InShot Video Editor Music, Cut</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/InShot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="InShot Video Editor Music, Cut" /><published>2015-08-17T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2015-08-17T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/InShot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/InShot.html">&lt;p&gt;InShot - Handy, Comprehensive and Fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trim video&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cut/Delete middle part of a video&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Merge videos&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adjust video speed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For Instagram.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Blur border for photo and video. Make it square ready for Instagram.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Colored border to make it square ready.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Move video/photo inside the square.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Music , Effects &amp;amp; Voice-overs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add your own music to video, like mp3 files and other format.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of fun sound effects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add voice-overs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easy to sync sound and video, with timeline features.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Volume control for both original video sound and mp3 songs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Text &amp;amp; Emoji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add your own music to video, like mp3 files and other format.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of fun sound effects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add voice-overs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easy to sync sound and video, with timeline features.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Volume control for both original video sound and mp3 songs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Filters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of Photo filters&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unique Video filters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rotate, Flip photo or video.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Photo Collage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High video output resolution.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Share to social apps, like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, WhatsApp, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h3 id=&quot;app-screenshots&quot;&gt;App Screenshots&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/inshot1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/inshot2.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/inshot3.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-it-in-the-app-store&quot;&gt;Get it in the App Store&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/US/app/id997362197?mt=8&amp;amp;at=11lGBA&amp;amp;ct=IS_R5&quot;&gt;InShot Video Editor Music, Cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">InShot - Handy, Comprehensive and Fun!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/inshot.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/inshot.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Control Your World: IFTTT</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/IFTTT.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Control Your World: IFTTT" /><published>2015-01-06T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2015-01-06T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/IFTTT</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/IFTTT.html">&lt;p&gt;Featuring Applets, IFTTT allows you to control everything around you with your voice and Amazon Alexa. To date, there are over 360 apps that work with IFTTT, including Twitter, Weather, Email, and devices like Amazon Alexa, and Philips Hue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find What You Want.&lt;/strong&gt; With the IFTTT, everything you want is just a few click away. Find the applets you already use – or want to use with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By App.&lt;/strong&gt; You can easily find applets by app or device. Find the applets already created for one of these or find new ones. Or create your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Search.&lt;/strong&gt; Search shouldn’t have to be difficult, and it’s not in the IFTTT app. You’ll always know which applets you’re already using and find new ones that might interest you based on your past experience. Your​ only limitation is your imagination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it-about&quot;&gt;What is it about?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is little that IFTTT can’t do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-wo-love-it&quot;&gt;Why wo love it&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re looking for a little order in your busy life, use IFTTT. It makes life so much easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-screenshots&quot;&gt;App Screenshots&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/IFTTT1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/IFTTT2.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/IFTTT3.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/IFTTT4.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-store-description&quot;&gt;App Store Description&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applets bring your favorite services together to create new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over 500 apps work with IFTTT including Twitter, Telegram, Google Drive, Twitch, Weather Underground, Instagram, Gmail, and devices like Google Home, Amazon Alexa, Nest, Philips Hue, and your iPhone. The IFTTT app also integrates with the Health app, so you can easily track and maintain your habits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-it-in-the-app-store&quot;&gt;Get it in the App Store&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/app/id660944635?mt=8&amp;amp;at=11lGBA&amp;amp;ct=IS_R5&quot;&gt;IFTTT: Control Your World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Featuring Applets, IFTTT allows you to control everything around you with your voice and Amazon Alexa. To date, there are over 360 apps that work with IFTTT, including Twitter, Weather, Email, and devices like Amazon Alexa, and Philips Hue.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/IFTTT.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/IFTTT.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Enlight Quickshot: The only camera app you’ll ever need</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/enlightQuickshot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Enlight Quickshot: The only camera app you’ll ever need" /><published>2014-12-26T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2014-12-26T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/enlightQuickshot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/enlightQuickshot.html">&lt;p&gt;The only camera app you’ll ever need.
Lightricks, and the Enlight app name, have become synonymous with excellent photo editing. With the latest app in the developer’s stable, the names are going to become known for taking great pictures, too&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The camera that rotates with you. Lightricks recognizes how frustrating it can be getting a straight shot by hand, and has included a Quickshot mode that automatically aligns photos and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Batch edit your photos. You can batch edit up to three photos in the free version, or many more with the pro subscription of Quickshot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plenty of filters to choose from. Lightricks Enlight is known for its plentiful filters, and Quickshot is no exception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it-about&quot;&gt;What is it about?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using Enlight for quite some time, moving over to Enlight 2 Photofox when it released. Because of the ease of use and plentiful features Lightricks includes in its apps, they’ve become my go-to choices for photo editing of all sorts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-wo-love-it&quot;&gt;Why wo love it&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, sometimes you don’t want to rely on Quickshot mode. You want an HDR image, or need to capture fast-moving action with the Strobe mode. When you edit your photos, you want ease of operations there, too. Enlight has become well-known for offering plenty of filters and adjustment controls, and Quickshot is no exception. Almost all of the filters come free with the app. There are filters for nature and urban settings, as well as portrait filters you can use. That’s only the beginning. Other filter categories include summer, abstract, night, and black &amp;amp; white. You can enjoy professional-level editing without the hassle of learning all the terms and controls. You also have at your fingertips almost all of the power of the Enlight app itself, along with an excellent camera app. You can adjust brightness, exposure, depth, shadows, highlights, and more. Add more vibrance to your images, adjust the saturation, or change the temperature of the lighting. Full control over your images is included right there, so you can make that boring, drab but essential picture come to life. Here’s the best part. Enlight Quickshot includes batch editing, so you can apply the same filter or settings to several photographs. Without a subscription, you’re limited to batch editing just three photos, but with the subscription option you can also create your own personalized filters that you save for future use, while also being able to batch edit as many photos as you can tap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-screenshots&quot;&gt;App Screenshots&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;    
&lt;a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/enlightQuickshot1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/enlightQuickshot2.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/enlightQuickshot3.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/blog/enlightQuickshot4.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;app-store-description&quot;&gt;App Store Description&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enlight Quickshot will make you fall in love with mobile photography. Here to convince you that the camera in your pocket is the only one you’ll ever need, Quickshot combines speed, simplicity and power into one streamlined app that just makes photo editing easier. Choose from our unique collection of customizable, handcrafted filters or create your own signature style, then apply to all your photos at once to give them a professional film-inspired look and feel. Download now and find out how simple superior photo editing can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-it-in-the-app-store&quot;&gt;Get it in the App Store&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/US/app/id1254875992?mt=8&amp;amp;at=11lGBA&amp;amp;ct=IS_R5&quot;&gt;Enlight Quickshot: The only camera app you’ll ever need&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">The only camera app you’ll ever need. Lightricks, and the Enlight app name, have become synonymous with excellent photo editing. With the latest app in the developer’s stable, the names are going to become known for taking great pictures, too</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/enlightQuickshot.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/enlightQuickshot.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>